<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marios Kogias</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Marios Kogias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://example.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 11:51:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 11:51:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Conferences  R2P2: Making RPCs first-class datacenter citizens Marios Kogias, George Prekas, Adrien Ghosn, Jonas Fietz, Ed Bugnion in Usenix ATC 2019 Paper Lancet: A self-correcting Latency Measuring Tool Marios Kogias, Stephen Mallon, Ed Bugnion in Usenix ATC 2019 Paper ZygOS: Achieving Low Tail Latency for Microsecond-scale Networked Tasks George Prekas*, Marios Kogias*, Ed Bugnion (*equal co-authors) in SOSP 2017 Paper  Workshops  Flow Control for Latency-Critical RPCs Marios Kogias, Ed Bugnion in KBNets@SIGCOMM2018 Paper  Posters  Measuring Latency: Am I doing it right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 11:49:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>R2P2 Our work on ZygOS revealed the mismatch between TCP&#39;s streaming semantics and RPCs&amp;rsquo; message-oriented semantics. R2P2 (Request Response Pair Protocol) is a transport protocol specifically designed for datacenter RPCs. It exposes a request and response abstraction, as opposed to streams or messages, and allows for in-network policy enforcement based on software and hardware middleboxes. R2P2 was presented in Usenix ATC 2019
 Source Code
Lancet Doing research in the μs-scale requires tools with the equivalent accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>