<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marios Kogias</title>
    <link>https://marioskogias.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Marios Kogias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://marioskogias.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://marioskogias.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 11:51:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marioskogias.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Studying in EPFL gives me several opportunities for teaching and mentoring students.
TAing  Principles of Computer Systems CS-522 (Winter 2017,2018,2019) Introduction to Operating Systems CS-323 (Spring 2019) Database Systems CS-422 (Spring 2018) Mise a Niveau MAN (Spring 2017) Computer Networks COM-208 (Winter 2016)  Student Mentoring Master Thesis  Martin Weber, Measuring Network Service Latencies with a Programmable Dataplane, Thesis PDF Antoine Albertelli, R3P2: a Replicated Request-Response Pair Protocol, Thesis PDF Ogier Bouvier, A Zero Copy Key-Value Store in Rust Lisa Zhou, Storage in IX: a High Performance Storage Layer for a Dataplane Operating System, Thesis PDF  Master Projects  Mikael Morales Gonzalez, R2P2 and UDP support in Lancet, Report Martin Weber, Introducing scheduling decisions in cooperative multitasking: an automated approach, Report Konstantinos Tsitsimpikos, Tail Latency Analysis on Fanout DataCenter Systems, Report Sutandi, I Made Sanadhi, QUIC Overview, Report  Bachelor Projects  Charline Montial, Webserver benchmarking with Lancet, Report  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://marioskogias.github.io/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 11:51:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marioskogias.github.io/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Conferences  HovercRaft: Achieving Scalability and Fault-tolerance for microsecond-scale Datacenter Services Marios Kogias, Ed Bugnion in Eurosys 2020 Paper R2P2: Making RPCs first-class datacenter citizens Marios Kogias, George Prekas, Adrien Ghosn, Jonas Fietz, Ed Bugnion in Usenix ATC 2019 Paper Lancet: A self-correcting Latency Measuring Tool Marios Kogias, Stephen Mallon, Ed Bugnion in Usenix ATC 2019 Paper ZygOS: Achieving Low Tail Latency for Microsecond-scale Networked Tasks George Prekas*, Marios Kogias*, Ed Bugnion (*equal co-authors) in SOSP 2017 Paper  Workshops  Flow Control for Latency-Critical RPCs Marios Kogias, Ed Bugnion in KBNets@SIGCOMM2018 Paper  Posters  SLOG: Your switch is also your load-generator Marios Kogias, Marti Weber, Ed Bugnion in NSDI 2020 Poster Measuring Latency: Am I doing it right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://marioskogias.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 11:49:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marioskogias.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>R2P2 Our work on ZygOS revealed the mismatch between TCP&#39;s streaming semantics and RPCs&amp;rsquo; message-oriented semantics. R2P2 (Request Response Pair Protocol) is a transport protocol specifically designed for datacenter RPCs. It exposes a request and response abstraction, as opposed to streams or messages, and allows for in-network policy enforcement based on software and hardware middleboxes. R2P2 was presented in Usenix ATC 2019
 Source Code
Lancet Doing research in the μs-scale requires tools with the equivalent accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>